are you looking for a dump insurance
plan which financially protects your
wife and children introducing ICICI
proof
I protect smart and it's seven benefits
that you must know first I protect smart
premium comfortably fits into your
budget even after paying off all your
monthly bills just what your wallet
asked for
second the sooner you buy term plan
online the better off you will be
premiums will be lower and cover will be
longer till the age of 75 third I
protect smart gives you option for full
claim payout on the first diagnosis of
any of 34 critical illnesses no hospital
bills required that's correct
no bills just a photocopy of your
diagnosis report will do more over this
option covers you for 30 years without
any change in premium
fourth I protect smart gives your
nominees for ways to receive insurance
money first lump sum second regular
monthly income third increasing monthly
income and the newly launched lump sum
plus regular monthly income thus all the
important needs of your children and
wife are met on time fifth I protect
smart in all its plan options helps you
put up a big fight against major
terminal illnesses including AIDS by
paying the insurance money before death
sixth you may add the accidental death
benefit in I protect smart during or
after the purchase of the policy with
the maximum cover up to rupees two
crores seven I protect smart gives you
the option to buy the policy online
under mwp Act the married women Property
Act helps provide protection against
wrongful claims so that the insurance
amount goes to no one else but only to
your wife and children
go get the seven fold protection online
today
[Music]